[
  {"question"  : "A",
   "answer"    :["c1","i1","inter","i3"],
   "id"        : 0 
  },
  {"question"  : "B",
   "answer"    : ["c2","i1","inter","i2"],
   "id"        : 1
  },
  {"question"  : "NOT A",
   "answer"    : ["c2","c3","i2","uni"],
   "id"        : 2
  },
  {"question"  :"NOT B",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c3","i3","uni"],
   "id"        : 3  
  },
  {"question"  : "A OR B",
   "answer"    :["c1","c2","i1","i2","i3","inter"],
   "id"        : 4 
  },
  {"question"  : "B OR C",
   "answer"    : ["c3","c2","i1","i2","inter","i3"],
   "id"        : 5
  },
  {"question"  :"A AND B",
   "answer"    : ["i1","inter"],
   "id"        : 6  
  },
  {"question"  :"NOT C",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c2","i1","uni"],
   "id"        : 7 
  },
  {"question"  : "NOT (A OR B OR C)",
   "answer"    : ["uni"],
   "id"        : 8
  },
  {"question"  : "Well Done!! Go to the next level...",
   "answer"    : [""],
   "id"        : 9
  }
]

